A Guide to the Records of the President's Office, Virginia Union University 1934-1999
Archives and Special Collections Department, L. Douglas Wilder Library, Virginia Union University
- Series II
  - Choral Concerts, (2/3) (Box-folder 4:38)
  - Choral Concerts, (3/3) (Box-folder 4:39)
  - Christmas Card Information (Box-folder 4:40)
  - Christmas Contest (Box-folder 4:41)
  - Christmas Dinner (Box-folder 4:42)
  - CIAA Basketball (Box-folder 4:43)
  - Class Gifts (Box-folder 4:44)
  - Class Presidents (Box-folder 4:45)
  - Class Presidents' Correspondence (Box-folder 4:46)
  - Class Presidents' Dinner (Box-folder 4:47)
  - Class Reunion, (1/2) (Box-folder 4:48)
  - Class Reunion, (2/2) (Box-folder 4:49)
  - Class Reunion 1923 (Box-folder 4:50)
  - Class Reunion Gifts (Box-folder 4:51)
  - Class of 1924 (Box-folder 5:1)
  - Class of 1927 (Box-folder 5:2)
  - Class of 1928 (Box-folder 5:3)
  - Class of 1929 (Box-folder 5:4)
  - Class of 1930 (Box-folder 5:5)
  - Class of 1931 (Box-folder 5:6)
  - Class of 1932 (Box-folder 5:7)
  - Class of 1933 (Box-folder 5:8)
  - Class of 1934 (Box-folder 5:9)
  - Class of 1935 (Box-folder 5:10)
  - Class of 1936 (Box-folder 5:11)
  - Class of 1942 (Box-folder 4:12)
  - Class of 1943 (Box-folder 5:13)
  - Class of 1944 (Box-folder 5:14)
  - Class of 1947 (Box-folder 5:15)
  - Class of 1954 (Box-folder 5:16)
  - Class of 1958 (Box-folder 5:17)
  - Class of 1962 (Box-folder 5:18)
  - Class of 1981 (Box-folder 5:19)
  - Class of 1986 (Box-folder 5:20)
  - Classes Academic Requirement (Box-folder 5:21)
  - Classification (Box-folder 5:22)
  - Cluster Meeting (Box-folder 5:23)
  - Coat of Arms (Box-folder 5:24)
  - Coburn Hall Completion Campaign (Box-folder 5:25)
  - Codes (Box-folder 5:26)
  - Co-ed Visitation Proposal (Box-folder 5:27)
  - Collateral Accounts (Box-folder 5:28)
  - College Cost Survey (Box-folder 5:29)
  - College Presidents (Box-folder 5:30)
  - Commencement 1960 (Box-folder 5:31)
  - Commencement 1970-71 (Box-folder 5:32)
  - Commencement 1973-74 (Box-folder 5:33)
  - Commencement 1976 (Box-folder 5:34)
  - Commencement 1979 (Box-folder 5:35)
  - Commencement 1980 (Box-folder 5:36)
  - Commencement 1981 (Box-folder 5:37)
  - Commencement 1982 (Box-folder 5:38)
  - Commencement 1983 (Box-folder 5:39)
  - Commencement 1984 (Box-folder 5:40)
  - Commencement 1985 (Box-folder 5:41)
  - Commencement 1986 (Box-folder 5:42)
  - Commencement 1987 (Box-folder 5:43)
  - Commencement 1996 (Box-folder 5:44)
  - Committee- Academic Advisory (Box-folder 5:45)
  - Committee- Academic Affairs, (1/2) (Box-folder 5:46)
  - Committee- Academic Affairs, (2/2) (Box-folder 5:47)
  - Committee- Academic Improvement (Box-folder 4:48)
  - Committee- Academic Policy (Box-folder 5:49)
  - Committee- Academic Steering (Box-folder 5:50)
  - Committee- Ad Hoc Curriculum Review (Box-folder 5:51)
  - Committee- Ad Hoc PME (Box-folder 5:52)
  - Committee- Ad Hoc Promotions and Tenure (Box-folder 5:53)
  - Committee- Ad Hoc Richmond Community Hospital (Box-folder 5:54)
  - Committee- Admissions (Box-folder 5:55)
  - Committee- Advisory Council for Health Related Professionals (Box-folder 5:56)
  - Committee- Alumni (Box-folder 5:57)
  - Committee- Alumni Affair (Box-folder 5:58)
  - Committee- Alumni Director Search (Box-folder 5:59)
  - Committee- Assignments (Box-folder 6:1)
  - Committee- Athletics, (1/2) (Box-folder 6:2)
  - Committee- Athletics, (2/2) (Box-folder 6:3)
  - Committee- Awards (Box-folder 6:4)
  - Committee- Beautification (Box-folder 6:5)
  - Committee- Bicentennial (Box-folder 5:6)
  - Committee- Blue Ribbon (Box-folder 6:7)
  - Committee- Book (Box-folder 6:8)
  - Committee- Brown, Homer S. (Box-folder 6:9)
  - Committee- Budget Review (Box-folder 6:10)
  - Committee- Cafeteria (Box-folder 6:11)
  - Committee- Calendar (Box-folder 6:12)
  - Committee- Chavis, Jesse Jr. (Box-folder 6:13)
  - Committee- Coburn Hall (Box-folder 6:14)
  - Committee- Commencement (Box-folder 6:15)
  - Committee- Committees (Box-folder 6:16)
  - Committee- Counseling Center (Box-folder 6:17)
  - Committee- Curriculum (Box-folder 6:18)
  - Committee- Electronic Data Processing (Box-folder 6:19)
  - Committee- Executive Search, (1/2) (Box-folder 6:20)
  - Committee- Executive Search, (2/2) (Box-folder 6:21)
  - Committee- Faculty Evaluation (Box-folder 6:22)
  - Committee- Faculty Executive, (1/2) (Box-folder 5:23)
  - Committee- Faculty Executive, (2/2) (Box-folder 6:24)
  - Committee- Faculty Fringe Benefits (Box-folder 6:25)
  - Committee- Faculty Handbook (Box-folder 6:26)
  - Committee- Faculty Meeting (Box-folder 6:27)
  - Committee- Faculty Rank (Box-folder 6:28)
  - Committee- Faculty Search (Box-folder 6:29)
  - Committee- Faculty Senate (Box-folder 6:30)
  - Committee- Faculty Travel (Box-folder 6:31)
  - Committee- Financial Aid (Box-folder 6:32)
  - Committee- Fine Arts (Box-folder 6:33)
  - Committee- Food Service (Box-folder 6:34)
  - Committee- General Ed. (Box-folder 6:35)
  - Committee- Graduate Assistance (Box-folder 6:36)
  - Committee- Grievance (Box-folder 6:37)
  - Committee- Homecoming (Box-folder 6:38)
  - Committee- Honors (Box-folder 6:39)
  - Committee- Inaugural (Box-folder 6:40)
  - Committee- Institutional Research (Box-folder 6:41)
  - Committee- Interim Academic Affairs (Box-folder 6:42)
  - Committee- Loss Prevention Safety (Box-folder 6:43)
  - Committee- Mission, Goals and Objects (Box-folder 6:44)
  - Committee- Parents Weekend (Box-folder 6:45)
  - Committee- Parking Security and Parking Board (Box-folder 6:46)
  - Committee- Pest Infestation Task Force (Box-folder 6:47)
  - Committee- Pres. Search (Box-folder 6:48)
  - Committee- Promotions and Tenure (Box-folder 6:49)
  - Committee- Recognition (Box-folder 6:50)
  - Committee- Recruitment (Box-folder 6:51)
  - Committee- Reports Beginning: 1969-1970 Academic Year (Box-folder 6:52)
  - Committee- Reports 1971 (Box-folder 6:53)
  - Committee- Safety (Box-folder 6:54)
  - Committee- Salary Scale (Box-folder 6:55)
  - Committee- Search (Box-folder 6:56)
  - Committee- Search for Admission and Financial Aid (Box-folder 6:57)
  - Committee- Search Allied Health Program Director (Box-folder 7:1)
  - Committee- Search, Assistant Chief Fiscal and Personnel Officer (Box-folder 7:2)
  - Committee- Search for Athletic Director (Box-folder 7:3)
  - Committee- Search in Biology (Box-folder 7:4)
  - Committee- Search for Chief Fiscal Officer Assistant (Box-folder 7:5)
  - Committee- Search for Comptroller (Box-folder 7:6)
  - Committee- Search, Counseling (Box-folder 7:7)
  - Committee- Search, Dean School of Theology (Box-folder 7:8)
  - Committee- Search for D.C. (Box-folder 7:9)
  - Committee- Search, Dean of Students (Box-folder 7:10)
  - Committee- Search for Director of Counseling and Student Development (Box-folder 7:11)
  - Committee- Search for Director of School of Education and Psychology (Box-folder 7:12)
  - Committee- Search for Faculty in Computer Science (Box-folder 7:13)
  - Committee- Search for Instructors, Political Science (Box-folder 7:14)
  - Committee- Search for Librarian (Box-folder 7:15)
  - Committee- Search for Professor of Philosophy (Box-folder 7:16)
  - Committee- Search, Records Coordinator (Box-folder 7:17)
  - Committee- Search, SLSBA (Box-folder 7:18)
  - Committee- Search, Sociology/ Social Work (Box-folder 7:19)
  - Committee- Search, Student Development (Box-folder 7:20)
  - Committee- Search, STVU (Box-folder 7:21)
  - Committee- Search, Vice President Academic Affairs (Box-folder 7:22)
  - Committee- Service Awards (Box-folder 7:23)
  - Committee- Special Ed (Box-folder 7:24)
  - Committee - Standing (Box-folder 7:25)
  - Committee- Student Publications (Box-folder 7:26)
  - Committee- Student Relation (Box-folder 7:27)
  - Committee- Student Service Search (Box-folder 7: 28)
  - Committee- Summer School (Box-folder 7:29)
  - Teacher Evaluation (Box-folder 7:30)
  - University Hostesses (Box-folder 7:31)
  - Community- University Life (Box-folder 7:32)
  - Communications Bulletin (Box-folder 7:33)
  - Communications Channels (Box-folder 7:34)
  - Communication from President (Box-folder 7:35)
  - Communications Sessions (Box-folder 7:36)
  - Community College Systems for Va. Union Univ. (Box-folder 7:37)
  - Community Directors (Box-folder 7:38)
  - Community of Scholar (Box-folder 7:39)
  - Competencies (Box-folder 7:40)
  - Complaints (Box-folder 7:41)
  - Comptroller Position (Box-folder 7:42)
  - Computer Center/ Guide Book (Box-folder 7:43)
  - Computer Center Layout (Box-folder 7:44)
  - Computer Center Service Plan (Box-folder 7:45)
  - Computer Lab Hours (Box-folder 7:46)
  - Concerns (Box-folder 7:47)
  - Concept Paper (Box 7:48)
  - Conference - Foreign Policy (Box-folder 7:49)
  - Confidential (Box-folder 7:50)
  - Continuing Education (Box-folder 7:51)
  - Contract Agreements (Box-folder 6:52)
  - Contractual Services (Box-folder 7:53)
  - Convocation (Box-folder 7:54)
  - Convocation of Recognition (Box-folder 7:55)
  - Cooperative Education Program (Box-folder 7:56)
  - Cooperative Education Student Handbook (Box-folder 7:57)
  - Cost of College Education at Virginia Union University (Box-folder 7:58)
  - Cost Per Credit Hour (Box-folder 7:59)
  - Council of Independent Colleges in Virginia (Box-folder 7:60)
  - Council of Independent Colleges in Virginia. Annual Enrollment Study 1986 (Box-folder 7:61)
  - Council of Independent Colleges in Virginia. Application, Admission and Enrollment (Box-folder 7:62)
  - Council of Independent Colleges/ Surveys (Box-folder 7:63)
  - Council on Religion (Box-folder 7:64)
  - Counselors Conference (Box-folder 7:65)
  - Courses - New (Box-folder 7:66)
  - Courses off Campus ( at other schools) (Box-folder 7:67)
  - Course Offerings (Box-folder 7:68)
  - Course Waivers (Box-folder 7:69)
  - Credit Free Programs (Box-folder 7:70)
  - Credit Line (Box-folder 7:71)
  - Credits ( Co- Curricular) (Box-folder 7:72)
  - Crisis Situation (Box-folder 7:73)
  - Critical Needs (Box-folder 7:74)
  - Critical Thinking Course Outline (Box-folder 7:75)
  - Critiquing Forum (Box-folder 7:76)
  - Curriculum (Box-folder 7:77)
  - Curriculum Precessions (Box-folder 7:78)
  - Dance Troupe (Box-folder 8:1)
  - Dean's List (Box-folder 8:2)
  - Debating (Box-folder 8:3)
  - Dedication (Box-folder 8:4)
  - Deficit Plan of Liquidate (Box-folder 8:5)
  - Definitions (Box-folder 8:6)
  - Degrees Granted and Other Degree Info (Box-folder 8:7)
  - Delinquent Accounts (Box-folder 8:8)
  - Departments (Box-folder 8:9)
  - Developing Institutions (Box-folder 8:10)
  - Development (Box-folder 8:11)
  - Development Council (Box-folder 8:12)
  - Development Large Gifts (Box-folder 8:13)
  - Development- Lawson and Williams (Box-folder 8:14)
  - Development- McLean Stepehn (Box-folder 8:15)
  - Development News (Box-folder 8:16)
  - Development- Phase II (Box-folder 8:17)
  - Development Press Release (Box-folder 8:18)
  - Development Program (Box-folder 8:19)
  - Development Program Projects (Box-folder 8:20)
  - Development Workshop (Box-folder 8:21)
  - Dinner (Box-folder 8:22)
  - Diploma (Box-folder 8:23)
  - Directors (Box-folder 8:24)
  - Distinguished Professors (Box-folder 8:25)
  - Distinguished Scholars-in-Residence (Box-folder 8:26)
  - Divisions (Box-folder 8:27)
  - Doctoral Degree Candidates (Box-folder 8:28)
  - Doctorate Degrees (Box-folder 8:29)
  - Doctor of Ministry Program (Box-folder 8:30)
  - Document- Academic Jounalism (Box-folder 8:31)
  - Document- Accounting Policies and Procedures (Box-folder 8:32)
  - Document- Adjunct Faculty Handbook 1986 (Box-folder 8:33)
  - Document- Adjunct Faculty Handbook 1987 (Box-folder 8:34)
  - Document- Administration Average Salaries (Box-folder 8:35)
  - Document- Administrative and Faculty Committees (Box-folder 8:36)
  - Document- Administrative/ Fiscal/ Financial Matters (Box-folder 8:37)
  - Document- Admissions Alumni Affairs Network (Box-folder 8:38)
  - Document- Admissions Packets (Box-folder 8:39)
  - Document- Affirmative Action Policy (Box-folder 8:40)
  - Document- Annual Report 1990-1991 (Box-folder 8:41)
  - Document- Annual Report/ Unit Directors 1989-1990, (1/2) (Box-folder 8:42)
  - Document- Annual Report/ Unit Directors 1989-1990, (2/2) (Box-folder 8:43)
  - Document- Application Changes (Box-folder 8:44)
  - Document- Average Faculty Salary (Box-folder 8:45)
  - Document- Black on Black Crime Winter Summit (Box-folder 8:46)
  - Document- Budgets, Virginia Union University 1984-1990 (Box-folder 8:47)
  - Document- Budgets, Executive V.P. 1989-1990 (Box-folder 8:48)
  - Document- Budgets, Executive V.P. 1990-1991 (Box-folder 8:49)
  - Document- Budgets, Executive V.P. 1991-1992 (Box-folder 8:50)
  - Document-Change of Major (Box-folder 8:51)
  - Document-Commencement Marching Policy (Box-folder 8:52)
  - Document-Critical Needs Project (Box-folder 8:53)
  - Document- CSAP 1991 (Box-folder 8:54)
  - Document- Data Base Authorization List (Box-folder 8:55)
  - Document- Data Shelter (Box-folder 8:56)
  - Document- Declared Major's Report Data (Box-folder 8:57)
  - Document- Dept. Of Education (Box-folder 8:58)
  - Document- Development/ Campaign Figures, (charts) (Box-folder 8:59)
  - Document- Drug Free Workplace (Box-folder 8:60)
  - Document- Endowed Scholarship's Criteria (Box-folder 8:61)
  - Document- Enrollment (Box-folder 8:62)
  - Document- Enrollment Data (Box-folder 8:63)
  - Document- Enrollment Figures (Box-folder 8:64)
  - Document- Enrollment Numbers 85-89 (Box-folder 8:65)
  - Document- 501 3 Tax Exempt Letter (Box-folder 8:66)
  - Document- Employee Nationality (Box-folder 8:67)
  - Document- Equipment Inventory (Box-folder 8:68)
  - Document- Facility Rental (Box-folder 8:69)
  - Document- Fact Book (Box-folder 8:70)
  - Document- Faculty Class (Box-folder 9:1)
  - Document- Faculty Handbook 1979 (Box-folder 9:2)
  - Document- Faculty Handbook 1981 (Box-folder 9:3)
  - Document- Faculty Handbook 1986 (Box-folder 9:4)
  - Document- Faculty Handbook 1990 (Box-folder 9:5)
  - Document- Financial Aid (Box-folder 9:6)
  - Document- Financial Aid 1988-1989 (Box-folder 9:7)
  - Document- Financial Aid GSL (Box-folder 9:8)
  - Document- Fire Drill Procedures (Box-folder 9:9)
  - Document- Grade Distribution (Box-folder 9:10)
  - Document- Graduate Directory (Box-folder 9:11)
  - Document- Guidelines for Writing Goals (Box-folder 9:12)
  - Document- Hawkins, Augustus Correspondence (Box-folder 9:13)
  - Document- HBCU Grant Formula (Box-folder 9:14)
  - Document- HBCU 100 Plus Book Directory Questionnaire (Box-folder 9:15)
  - Document- Higher Education Day/ First Baptist (Box-folder 9:16)
  - Document- Housing Project (Box-folder 9:17)
  - Document- Hovey Field Rental (Box-folder 9:18)
  - Document- IBM Award (Box-folder 9:19)
  - Document- IBM Equipment Grant (Box-folder 9:20)
  - Document- Institutional Profile 1989 (Box-folder 9:21)
  - Document- Institutional Profile 1990 (Box-folder 9:22)
  - Document- Institutional/Program Eligibility (Box-folder 9:23)
  - Document- Investment Policy (Box-folder 9:24)
  - Document- IPEDS Report (Box-folder 9:25)
  - Document- Journal and Guide Symposium on Race (Box-folder 9:26)
  - Document- Kenan Procedure Manual (Box-folder 9:27)
  - Document- Kenan Procedure Expansion (Box-folder 9:28)
  - Document- Kenan Project (Box-folder 8:29)
  - Document- Kenan Project Annual Report 1987 (Box-folder 9:30)
  - Document- Kenan Project Newsletter (Box-folder 9:31)
  - Document- Kingsley Hall Project (Box-folder 9:32)
  - Document- Letter Writing Samples (Box-folder 9:33)
  - Document- Library African American Collection (Box-folder 9:34)
  - Document- NAFEO Enrollment Survey (Box-folder 9:35)
  - Document- NAFEO Profiles (Box-folder 9:36)
  - Document- New Beginnings Campaign (Box-folder 9:37)
  - Document- New Faculty Appointment 1989-1990 (Box-folder 9:38)
  - Document- Newsletter- Virginia Union University Reports (Box-folder 9:39)
  - Document- Parking and Driving Reg./Campus Police (Box-folder 9:40)
  - Document- Pell Grant Student Accounts (Box-folder 9:41)
  - Document- Proposal Monthly Activities (Box-folder 9:42)
  - Document- School of Theology Faculty Manual (Box-folder 9:43)
  - Document- School of Theology Student Manual (Box-folder 9:44)
  - Document-Staff Manual 1982 (Box-folder 9:45)
  - Document- Student Handbook 1989-91 (Box-folder 9:46)
  - Document- Students Registered, Not Cleared (Box-folder 9:47)
  - Document- Student Support Services Newsletter (Box-folder 9:48)
  - Document- Walker, Maggie High School Lease Agreement (Box-folder 9:49)
  - Dormitories, (1/2) (Box-folder 9:50)
  - Dormitories, (2/2) (Box-folder 9:51)
  - Dormitories Co-Ed Visitation (Box-folder 9:52)
  - Dormitories Grievances (Box-folder 9:53)
  - Dormitories- work Schedule (Box-folder 9:54)
  - Dormitory Capacities (Box-folder 8:55)
  - Dormitory Renovations (Box-folder 9:56)
  - Dormitory Roster (Box-folder 9:57)
  - Dream Team (Box-folder 9:58)
  - Dreams (for the future) (Box-folder 9:59)
  - Drug Abuse (Box-folder 9:60)
  - Ecosystem (Box-folder 9:61)
  - Educational Office Personnel (Box-folder 9:62)
  - Educational Support Staff Standards (Box-folder 9:63)
  - Elevator (Box-folder 9:64)
  - Ellison, John M. Scholarship Fund (Box-folder 9:65)
  - Employee Benefits (Box-folder 10:1)
  - Employee 5 or more years (Box-folder 10:2)
  - Employment Off Campus (Box-folder 10:3)
  - Employment Policy (Box-folder 10:4)
  - Employment Policy Statement (Box-folder 10:5)
  - English Essay (Box-folder 10:6)
  - Enrollment (Box-folder 10:7)
  - Enrollment (Box-folder 10:8)
  - Enrollment (Box-folder 10:9)
  - Enrollment 1966-1982 (Box-folder 10:10)
  - Enrollment Command (Box-folder 10:11)
  - Enrollment Figures 1974-1984 (Box-folder 10:12)
  - Enrollment History 1900-1981 (Box-folder 10:13)
  - Enrollment Projections 1981-1988 (Box-folder 10:14)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity (Box-folder 10:15)
  - Equipment (Box-folder 10:16)
  - Estate Planning Advisory Council (Box-folder 10:17)
  - Evaluation of Academic Programs (Box-folder 10:18)
  - Evaluations (Box-folder 10:19)
  - Evaluations Computer Center (Box-folder 10:20)
  - Evaluative Criteria for Review of Academic Programs (Box-folder 10:21)
  - Evaluative and Pre-Planning Sessions (Box-folder 10:22)
  - Examination Permits Jan 1983 to [?] (Box-folder 10:23)
  - Examinations, Tests, Grading (Box-folder 10:24)
  - Exceptions Made (Box-folder 10:25)
  - Exchange Programs (Box-folder 10:26)
  - Executive Assistant to the President (Box-folder 10:27)
  - Executive Summary Reports 1985-1986 (Box-folder 10:28)
  - Facilities- Use of (Box-folder 10:29)
  - Facts (Box-folder 10:30)
  - Faculty (adjunct status) (Box-folder 10:31)
  - Faculty Advisors (Box-folder 10:32)
  - Faculty and Staff Directories 1986-1988 (Box-folder 10:33)
  - Faculty and Staff Directory 1989-1990 (Box-folder 10:34)
  - Faculty Appointment Slip (for reference) (Box-folder 10:35)
  - Faculty Awareness (Box-folder 10:36)
  - Faculty Confidential (Box-folder 10:37)
  - Faculty Constitution (Box-folder 10:38)
  - Faculty by Degree and Dep (Box-folder 10:39)
  - Faculty Development (Box-folder 10:40)
  - Faculty Dialogues (Box-folder 10:41)
  - Faculty- Employment (Non-University) (Box-folder 10:42)
  - Faculty Evaluations (Box-folder 10:43)
  - Faculty Evaluations 1983 June (Box-folder 10:44)
  - Faculty Evaluations 1984 June (Box-folder 10:45)
  - Faculty Evaluations by Students School of Ed. and Psych. (Box-folder 10:46)
  - Faculty Evaluations- School of Education (Box-folder 10:47)
  - Faculty Exchange (Box-folder 11:1)
  - Faculty Fellowships (Box-folder 11:2)
  - Faculty Handbook (Box-folder 11:3)
  - Faculty Handbook (Box-folder 11:4)
  - Faculty Handbook (Box-folder 11:5)
  - Faculty Professional Staff Profiles (Box-folder 11:6)
  - Faculty- Staff (Box-folder 11:7)
  - Faculty- Staff (Box-folder 11:8)
  - Faculty- Staff Bios (Box-folder 11:9)
  - Faculty- Staff Changes (Box-folder 11:10)
  - Faculty- Teaching Assignments (Box-folder 11:11)
  - Financial Aid Awards 1987-1988, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 11:12)
  - Fixed Asset Inventory (Box-folder 11:13)
  - Honorees Reception (Box-folder 11:14)
  - IBM Faculty or Loan (Box-folder 11:15)
  - IBM Project (Box-folder 11:16)
  - Institutional Profile (Box-folder 11:17)
  - Job Application- Secretarial (Box-folder 11:18)
  - Leave (Box-folder 11:19)
  - Library Services (Box-folder 11:20)
  - Library Survey (Box-folder 11:21)
  - Marketing Analysis Proposal- Consortium For Advancement of Private Higher Education (Box-folder 11:22)
  - Media General Statistical Report (Box-folder 11:23)
  - Milestone- L. Douglas Wilder (Box-folder 11:24)
  - Minutes (Box-folder 11:25)
  - Missions and Goals Statement (Box-folder 11:26)
  - Newsletter (Box-folder 11:27)
  - Operations Monitoring System (Box-folder 11:28)
  - Original Reports- Post School Conference (Box-folder 11:29)
  - Recommendations (Box-folder 11:30)
  - Residence Life (Box-folder 11:31)
  - Staff Employment (Box-folder 11:32)
  - Staff Handbook 1990 (Box-folder 11:33)
  - Surveys and Questionnaire (Box-folder 11:34)
- Series III
  - Annual Reports 1934-1936 (Box-folder 1:1)
  - Correspondence 1933-1935 (Box-folder 1:2)
  - The Distinct Aims and Program of the Church Related Colleges, paper by Clark presented to Home Mission Society Colleges 11 February 1939 (Box-folder 1:3)
  - Minutes, Board of Trustees Meeting 1935 (Box-folder 1:4)
  - Photographs (Box-folder 1:5)
  - TOPS magazine n.d. (Box-folder 1:6)